Renaissance architecture photograph collection (Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America)
Yale University Arts Library
- Architecture: Renaissance III. (Box 49)
  - Latin America., 1192 (Box 117)
    - Peru., 364 (Box 129)
      - Individual locations., 355 (Box 129)
        - Cuzco., 55 (Box 130)
          - Churches., 42 (Box 130)
            - Cathedral., 14 (Box 131)
            - Chincheros., 2 (Box 131)
            - La Compania., 10 (Box 131)
            - La Merced., 6 (Box 131)
            - La Recoleta., 2 (Box 131)
            - San Sebastian., 4 (Box 131)
          - Houses., 5 (Box 131)
        - Huancane., 1 (Box 131)
        - Ica., 1 (Box 131)
        - Juli., 21 (Box 131)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 131)
          - La Asuncion., 5 (Box 131)
          - Santa Cruz., 9 (Box 132)
          - San Juan., 3 (Box 132)
          - San Pedro Martir., 3 (Box 132)
        - Juliaca., 4 (Box 132)
        - Lambayeque., 2 (Box 132)
        - Lampa., 1 (Box 132)
        - Lima., 150 (Box 132)
          - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 11 (Box 132)
          - Churches., 102 (Box 132)
            - Miscellaneous churches., 17 (Box 132)
            - Cathedral., 2 (Box 132)
            - La Concepcion., 6 (Box 132)
            - San Agustin., 13 (Box 133)
            - Santo Domingo., 2 (Box 133)
            - San Francisco., 34 (Box 133)
              - Exterior., 19 (Box 133)
              - Interior., 15 (Box 133)
            - San Marcelo., 2 (Box 133)
            - San Pedro Nolesco., 3 (Box 133)
            - San Sebastian., 2 (Box 133)
            - Santa Teresa., 12 (Box 133)
            - Surco., 2 (Box 133)
            - Las Trinitarias., 2 (Box 133)
            - Virgen del Patrocinio., 5 (Box 134)
          - Government buildings., 5 (Box 134)
            - Local de la Inquisicion., 5 (Box 134)
          - Palaces., 21 (Box 134)
            - Miscellaneous palaces., 3 (Box 134)
            - Torre Tagle Palace., 18 (Box 134)
          - Schools., 4 (Box 134)
          - Streets., 7 (Box 134)
        - Oropesa., 2 (Box 134)
        - Pachacamac (Pueblo of)., 1 (Box 134)
        - Pisac., 6 (Box 134)
        - Pomata., 8 (Box 135)
        - Pucara., 2 (Box 135)
        - Puno., 3 (Box 135)
        - Sana., 4 (Box 135)
        - Trujillo., 3 (Box 135)
        - Yungayo., 1 (Box 135)
        - Zepita., 4 (Box 135)
    - Puerto Rico., 3 (Box 135)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 3 (Box 135)
        - Ponce., 1 (Box 135)
        - San German., 1 (Box 135)
        - San Juan., 1 (Box 135)
    - Venezuela., 6 (Box 135)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 6 (Box 135)
        - Barcelona., 1 (Box 135)
        - Carora., 1 (Box 135)
        - Coro., 1 (Box 135)
        - Piritu., 2 (Box 135)
        - San Carlos., 1 (Box 136)